[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first person to  use the term atomic bomb?", "correct_answer": "H.G. Wells", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Oppenheimer", "Lise Meitner", "Enrico Fermi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the Western black widow spider?", "correct_answer": "It is extremely venomous.", "incorrect_answers": ["The female always eats the male after mating.", "It is native to Madagascar.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This plantation located in Louisiana is said to be haunted by the vengeful ghost of a slave named Chloe, who supposedly murdered the wife and daughters of the owner.", "correct_answer": "Myrtles Plantation", "incorrect_answers": ["Laura Plantation", "Melrose Plantation", "Oak Alley Plantation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term of Indian origin refers to ones fate or destiny, as the result of ones actions.", "correct_answer": "karma", "incorrect_answers": ["samsara", "sarana", "nirvana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the treatment of what medical condition is the herb St Johns wort considered beneficial?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Depression", "Alcoholism", "Parkinsons disease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following was the first womens advocacy show?", "correct_answer": "Leave It To The Girls", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ladies Hour", "The Ladies Home Journal Hour", "Girl Talk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following languages is not an official language of the United Nations?", "correct_answer": "German", "incorrect_answers": ["Chinese", "Spanish", "Russian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what type of written form did Aristotle prefer to express and defend his doctrines?", "correct_answer": "Dialogue", "incorrect_answers": ["Fable", "Poetry", "Monologue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the deadliest jellyfish in the world?", "correct_answer": "Box Jellyfish", "incorrect_answers": ["Lions Mane Jellyfish", "Moon Jellyfish", "Sea Nettle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The city of Fargo is the largest city in which of these U.S. states?", "correct_answer": "North Dakota", "incorrect_answers": ["North Carolina", "South Dakota", "South Carolina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In ancient times, which stone was believed to protect from drunkenness?", "correct_answer": "amethyst", "incorrect_answers": ["ruby", "emerald", "onyx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the clothing brand Lacoste originally from?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada", "England", "U.S.A."]}]